Hello everyone! I'm in Hamburg this weekend and today I'm visiting Europe's
biggest erotic store Boutique Bizarre and I'll take you with me so come on!
I am now in the lingerie laundry department of the Boutique Bizarre.
I'm standing next to Andrea.
Hi.
Hello, nice to have you here.
How long has the shop been here?
The Boutique Bizarre has been around for over 30 years, but if you look around like that,
you're of course not boring at all.
I don't even know what to wear first, because you have so many things.
Yes, we wouldn't be able to make this difficult decision today.
You need a few hours to get through here in peace.
We have almost 30,000 products. I don't think I'll be able to fit that in today.
So of course I first had to check if I can find any catsuits, wet look catsuit, if you
know my channel you know why and I found one, I tried on and I quite like it, so it fits
but it is not the only one, there are dozens of catsuits here and dozens of wet look articles,
a lot of wet look fashion, fall fashion.
So there's really a lot to discover
and I can't wait to have a further look.
So, something colorful for a change
because a lot of black outfits here, which I totally love,
but I was thinking a bit brighter
And I saw a lot of designers and brands I know.
So a huge product range here.
And one thing I can totally recommend is ask the staff
if you have any questions with sizing and outfits
and different designers, different sizes,
because they can help you.
Ask them, they're super nice, they're super helpful.
I just found the masks.
And Julia from the Boutique Bizarre team,
you can tell me something about it,
because it's just mega cool.
Yes, exactly. This is an artist named Cecilio from Spain, who also makes masks for Lady Gaga,
Biosignals and Madonna.
I don't want to spoil her with makeup, so I'll just hold her.
Yes, great.
I feel ten steps cooler right away.
But I'll give you the good one back.
Thank you very much for that.
I'll keep looking around.
All right.
I think I saw this dress in the giveaway Fox Teufelswil did on Instagram and I know that
it is a boutique bizarre self-designed piece so I think I'm going to try this on as well.
This dress is designed by the boutique bizarre itself so they do have own products as well
and I do like this style. I'm not used to it to be honest because I'm used to having more fabric
but yeah this is cool and I think I'll go upstairs now.
This is the right case now, take it
Yeah
Deeper silence under the weakness
Not moving on would leave us faceless
We can scream popular, what's the problem?
If yes, maybe something's broken
Wonder why, wonder why I should believe it
From what I see, it's so much different
We never know, never know, never know why
Why everybody says, why everybody says
So I switched into a catsuit again. I don't know why I always end up with catsuits.
But I like the combination of mesh and PVC.
But since I don't want you to just try on catsuits, I'll head into the laundry section now.
Don't touch it.
I'm standing here with Klaus in the laundry department.
As they say, you are a real coryphan here.
You've been working here at the boutique Bizarre for a very long time.
Yes, 21 years.
21 years! Wow!
From the peak, so to speak, as a young man, I started here and I'm still here.
That's why I've snuck in with you now, because I have no idea what I could try.
Yes.
And you can definitely help me.
Definitely.
Okay, then let's get started.
Let's get started. I'm relying on you.
Yes, no problem!
I tried on several lingerie outfits and they're so beautiful and I love this coat.
It's not a coat, it's something else.
A nightgown maybe?
I don't know.
I don't think that the lingerie sets are really safe for YouTube so use your imagination or
have a look at the store here and check it yourself.
Should I try this one on?
Nah, it's not my style.
But you can get everything here, like these things as well.
But I'll check out some other stuff.
I switched into a latex outfit because it's the last outfit now.
And I thought, oh, let's try the structured latex.
super cool with all the skulls so you have a huge latex selection here as well and i don't know i
could have spent like 20 hours more here and try a lot of things on and have this awesome event
shopping experience here i can totally recommend it if you're in hamburg check out boutique bizarre
and yeah thanks to the whole team for having me and i'll have another look but without you so
see you in the next video